[
    {
        "front": "ポスター",
        "back": "advert",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "アルバイト",
        "back": "Part-time job",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "きぼう（する）",
        "back": "wish / to wish for",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "めんせつ",
        "back": "interview",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "うかがう",
        "back": "to call on / at",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しつれい（する）",
        "back": "to be sorry (apology)",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "もうす",
        "back": "(polite form of いう)",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "りれきしょ",
        "back": "resume",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "じむしょ",
        "back": "office",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "うら",
        "back": "back",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもて",
        "back": "front",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かざる",
        "back": "to display",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうひん",
        "back": "product",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "こわれる",
        "back": "to break (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）こわす",
        "back": "to break (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "さわる",
        "back": "to touch",
        "chapter": "N4 C13"
    }
]